Guide to the Time Inc. records Bio files 3009.RG2
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Schlamm, William S. (Box Bio108-Bio109)
  Two folders have a "H.R. Luce" stamp.
- SC
- Schiller, Larry (Lawrence)
- Schlender, Brent
- Schlesinger, Arthur M. Jr.
  One folder has a "H.R. Luce" stamp.
- Schnabel, Richard F.
- Scholl, Jane
- Schroeder, Ethel
- Schrier, Eric W.
- Schulberg, Budd
- Schulke, Flip
- Schurbert, Franz
- Schreiber, Le Anne
- Schonfeld, Reese
- Schurenberg, Eric
- Schutzer, Paul
- Schwartz, Alan
- Schwarz, Fred
- Schwarz, Mildred
- Schwindeman, Marian
- Scott, Francis M.
- Scott, Gavin
- Scott, John (Box Bio109-Bio110)
- Scott, Malcolm
- Scott, Mel
- Scull, Penrose
- Seabolt, Stephen J.
- Seagrave, Sterling
- Seaman, A. Barrett
- Seamon, Richard
- See, Henry W.
- Seiberling, Dorothy
- Seligman, Daniel
- Selznick, David
- Semel, Terry
- Senft, Craig T.
- Senie, Kevin
- Sermolino, Maria
- Servan-Schreiber, J.J.
- Serwer, Andrew
- Severeid, Eric
- Severinghaus, Sheldon
- Seixas, Suzanne (Sue)
- Seymour, James W. Jr.
- Seymour, David
- SH
- Shah of Iran
- Shahn, Ben
- Shaindlin, Jack
- Shannon, Elaine
- Shapiro, Walter F.
- Shaw, John F.
- Shaw, Mark
- Shay, Arthur
- Shea, Frank
- Shearer, John
- Sheehy, Gail
- Sheeler, Charles
- Sheets, Millard
- Sheldon, Don Young
- Shenker, Isreal
- Shenker, Mrs. Isreal (Mary)
- Sheperd, Dean
- Shepherd, James
- Shepley, James
  One folder contains a cassette tape labeled "James Shepley's Retirement Party".
- Sheppard, R.Z. (Ron)
- Sheppe, Peter
- Sheraton, Mimi
- Shere, Samuel
- Sherer, Betsy
- Sheridan, Bart
- Sherman, Cindy
- Sherrod, Robert (Box Bio111-Bio112)
- Sherwood, Robert
- Shetler, Richard L.
- Shields, Eileen
- Shipley, Mildred (Wallace)
- Shirley, Ernie
- Shnayerson, Robert
- Shook, Edgar
- Shrout, William Clay Jr.
- Shuker, Gregory B.
- Shute, James
- Shutt, George
- Sider, Don
- Sidey, Hugh
- Siekman, Philip
- Silberman, Charles
- Silk, George
- Silva, Michel (Mike)
- Silverman, Raissa
- Simmons, Ann
- Simmons, Roxane Ruhl
- Simms, Peter
- Silverman, Al
- Simon, James F. (Jim)
- Simon, Josh
- Simons, Mary
- Simpson, Cleary S.
- Simpson, Janice C.
- Sinclair, Christopher
- Singh, Anil
- Siskind, Aaron
- Siverd, Bonita (Bonnie)
- Skadding, George
- Skelly, Alan
- Skow, Jack
- Slagter, Ira R.
- Slater, Robert (Bob)
- Sloan, Alfred P.J.
- Slovinsky, Louis J.
- Smilgis, Martha J.
- Smith, Bradley
  Has an "H.R. Luce" stamp.
- Smith, Carol A.
- Smith, Charles D.
- Smith, Danyel
- Smith, David
- Smith, Edgar
- Smith, Fred
  One folder has an "H.R. Luce" stamp.
- Smith, Lillian
- Smith, Marshall
- Smith, Paul
- Smith, Richard Austin
- Smith, Robert H.
- Smith, Robert Stebbins
- Smith, Ruel
- Smith, Sally Bedell
- Smith, W. Eugene
- Smith, William
- Smith, Stephen
- Smith, William E
- Smith, William D.
- Smolan, Rick
- Smolowe, Jill
- Smucker, Virginia
- Snedaker, John R.
- Snell, David
- Snyder, Jerome
- Snow, C.P.
- Snow, Edgar
- Snowdon, Earl of
- Sochurek, Howard
- Sokolow, Diane
- Solberg, Carl Theodore
- Solow, Herbert
- Solzhenitsyn, Alexander
- Sookdeo, Ricardo
- Sousa, John Phillip III
- Sparks, Zona
- Speer, Albert
- Spelman, Franz
- Spencer, Terry
- Spieth, Dorethea
- Spink, Shepard
- Spurdle, Donald L.
- Squire, Lorene
- Squires, John
- Stackpole, Peter
- ST
- Stack, Alexander
- Stacks, John F.
- Stalin, Svetlana
- Stanley, Alessandra
- Stanton, John
- Stanush, Claude
- Stassen, Harold E.
- Stauffer, Donald
- Stebbins, John
- Steed, Robert
- Steele, John
- Steichan, Edward John
- Steinbauer, Mary
- Steinbreder Jr., Harry
- Steinbreder, John
- Steiner, Ralph
- Steinert, Eleanor
- Steinheimer, Charles
- Stengel, Richard
- Steinmann, Marion
- Stephenson, Michele
- Stern, Robert
- Stevens, Edmund W.
- Stevens, Geoffrey
- Stevens, Roy
- Stevenson, Adlai
- Stevenson, Gordon
- Stevenson, Matthew
- Stevenson, Pollygroves and John
- Stewart, Martha
- Stewart, William
- Stieglitz, Alfred
- Stillman, Charles (Box Bio114-Bio115)
- Stock, Dennis
- Stockly, Walter
- Stoler, Peter
- Stoller, Ezra
- Stolley, Richard B. (Dick)
- Stone, Edward Durrell (Box Bio116-Bio117)
- Stone, Roger
- Storey, John
- Story, George
- Stout, Elizabeth
- Straus, Patti
- Streibert, Theodore C.
- Streit, Clarence
- Striker, John F.
- Strock, George
- Stroud, Robert
- Strother, Robert
- Stuart, Lyle
- Sudler, Culbreth
- Sugar, Joseph M.
- Sugarman, Celia
- Sullivan, Louis Henry
- Sullivan, Irene A.
- Sullivan, Mark
- Sullivan, Robert
- Sumits, William J.
- Sumits, Bill
- Sund, Harold
- Suro, Roberto
- Suslock, Saul
- Sutter, Betty Satterwhite
- Sutton, Horace
- Sutton, Kelso
- Suydam, Henry
- Suyker, Betty
- Svedberg, Andrea
- Svirsky, Leon
- Susskind, David
- Swan, Analyn
- Swanson, Dick
- Swanson, Richard
- Sweeney, Robert
- Swift, Otis Peabody
- Swope, Herbert Bayard
- Swope, Martha
- Sykes, Jolene
- Symington, W. Stuart
- Synnott, Paul
- T
- Taber, George
- Tanuma, Takeyosi
- Taft, Robert
- Taft, Charles
- Talbott, Strobe
- Tarrant, Marguerite
- Tasker, J. Dana
- Tauris, Rosemarie
- Tax, Jerry
- Taylor, Alex
- Taylor, Olive
- Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilyich
- Teilhard, De Chardin
- Telemann, Georg Philipp
- Teller, Dr. Edward
- Temple, Arthur
- Temple, Arthur Jr.
- Tenney, Gordon
- Terkel, Studs
- Terrell, Roy
- Terry, Hugh
- Terry, Wallace
- Terry, Wallace H.
- Thai, Ted
- Themo, Mary
- Thimmesch, Nick
- Thomas, Byron
- Thomas, Evan
- Thomas, Richard B.
- Thomas, Stan
- Thomas, Stanley B. Jr.
- Tasker, J. Dana
- Thomason, Gus
- Thomason, James A. (Gus)
- Thompson, Craig
- Thompson, Dick
- Thompson, Edward K. (Box Bio119-Bio120)
- Thompson, Mark
- Thompson, Thomas W. (Tommy)
- Thomson, A.W.S. "Sandy"
- Thorkilsen, Eric
- Thorndike, Joseph (Jacobs) J.
- Thorn, John N.
- Thornhill, Arthur
- Thorsen, Karen
- Tibbs, John
- Thrasher, Corinne
  One folder has an "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Thurber, James
- Tibby, John
- Tinnin, David
- Tivnan, Edward
- Toepher, Susan
- Tolleris, Beatrice
- Tompkins, John S.
- Tompkins, Maurice C.
- Tourtellot, Arthur
- Tower, Whitney
- Toyn Bee, Arnold
- Trachtman, Paul
- Tracy, Eleanor Johnson
- Travis, June E.
- Treacy, Eleanor
- Tree, Marietta
- Trent, Brad
- Trent, William
- Tretick, Stan(ley)
- Trillin, Calvin
- Tripler, Veronica
- Trippett, Frank
- Trotsky, Leon
- Trowbridge, Jean Whiting
- Truman, Harry S.
- Tuchman, Barbara
- Tudor, Charles William
- Tudor, W. Pendleton (Pen)
- Tumulty, Karen
- Turnbull, James
- Turner, Ted
- Turner, Terry
- Tweedy, Mary (Johnson)
- Tyng, Lila (Mrs. H.R.L.)
- U
- Uebelhoer, Urban (Pete)
- Ullman, James Ramsey
- Underhill, John Garrett (Gary)
- Uttal, Bro
- Uzzle, Burk
- V
  Has an "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Valk, Elizabeth P.
- Valk, Garry
- Valk, Lisa
- Vallee, Rudy
- Vallely, Jean
- Van der Rohe, Mies
- Vandenberg, Arthur
- Vandenberg, Shedd
- Vanderschmidt, (F) Sydnor
- Vandivert, Rita
- Vandivert, William
- Van Fleet, Gen. James A.
- Van Meter, Isabella
- Van Meter, Jonathan
- Van Voorhis, Westbrook
- Van Voorst, Bruce
- Varga, Margit
- Vega, Marylois Purdy
- Venturi, Robert
- Vick Rey, Robert
- Videla, Gabriel Gonzales
- Viebranz, Curt
- Villet, Grey & Barbara
- Villet, Grey
- Vishinski, Andrei
- Vishniak, Mark (Box Bio122-Bio123)
- Vission, Anatole
- Vollmer, Karl F.
- Vollmuth, George H.
- Von Hoersheman, Natasha
- Von Hofmannsthal, Raimund
- Von Neumann, John
- Vrba, John
- WA
- Waber, Bernard
- Wainwright, Loudon
- Wakefield, Earle M.
- Walford, Crissy
- Walford, Christina
- Walker, Diana
- Walker, Hank
- Walker, John H.
- Wallace, Carol
- Wallace, Henry
- Wallace, Martha
- Wallace, N.L. (Box Bio123-Bio124)
- Wallace, Robert
- Wallis, Claudia
- Waln, Shelley Lewis
- Walsh, Denny
- Walsh, Michael
- Walton, Jane
- Walton, William
- Wanger, Walter
- Ward, Baldwin
- Warne, Jeanne
- Warnecke, John Carl
- Warner, Albert
- Warner family
- Warner Brothers (Albert, David, Harry, Jack L. & Sam L.)
- Warner, Bradford
- Warner, David
- Warner, Ed
- Warner, Edwin
- Warner, Harry M.
- Warner, Jack L.
- Warner, Mrs. Jack L. (Ann Page)
- Warner, Jack M(ilton) Jr.
- Warner, Rawleigh
- Warner, Samuel L.
- Waronker, Lenny
- Warren, Earl
- Warren, Robert Penn
- Wasserman, Bert
- Washburn, A(rthur) Lawrence
- Watson, Thomas J. Jr. (Box Bio124-Bio125)
- Watters, James
- Watters, Jim
- Waugh, Evelyn
- Wayman, Stan
- Ways, Max
- WE
- Weadon, Don
- Weaver, Paul H.
- Webber, Mildred
- Webber, W. Temple
- Webster, Dr. Bruce P.
- Webster, Norman
- Weeks, Brigitte
- Wehagen, Helen
- Weigel, Alice
- Weil, Louis A. "Chip"
- Weiss, Myron
- Weiss, Solomon
- Welch, Eleanor
- Welch, Mary
- Welch, Paul
- Welles, Christopher
- Wells, Louise (Baker) (Stroup)
- Welles, Orson
- Welles, Samuel
- Welsh, Mary (Hemingway)
- Wendt, Dr. Gerald
- Werkley, John G.
- Werner, Lucy
- Wertenbaker, Charles C.
- Wertenbaker, Green Peyton
- Wertenbaker, Lael
- West, Ellen
- West, Rebecca
- Westerfield, Putney
- Westfall, Sanra Sobieraj
- Westin, AV
- Westmoreland, William (Gen.)
- Wever, George
- WH
- Whalen, Richard
- Wharton, Clifton R.
- Wharton, Edith
- Wheeler, Dennis
- Wheeler, Keith
- Wheeler, Robert C.
- Wheelwright, Farley W.
- Whipple, A.B.C.
- White, Barbara
- White, E.B.
- White, Frank
- White, Jack
- White, Theodore (Box Bio126-Bio127)
- White, William Allen
- White, William Wesley
- Whitmore, James
- Whiting, David A.
- Whittingham, Charles
- Whittle, Chris
- Whyte, William H. Jr.
- Wickware, Frances
- Wiedmann, George
- Wiener, Leigh Austin
- Wierzynski, Gregory H.
- Wilde, James
- Wild, Hans
- Wilkes, Jack
- Willcox, Faith
- Williams, Monci Jo
- Williams, Nancy
- Williams, Phillip A.
- Williams, Richard
- Williams, Richard L.
- Williamson, Ben
- Willkie, Wendell
- Wills, Garry
- Willwerth, James
- Wilson, C.E.
- Wilson, Donald M.
- Wilson, Edward A.
- Wilson, Genevieve
- Wilson, Harold
- Wilson, Helen
- Wilson, Sloan
- Wilson, W. Dickinson
- Wilson, Woodrow
- Winchell, Walter
- Wind, Herbert Warren
- Windeler, Robert
- Winfrey, Carey W(ells)
- Wing, Michael
- Wingerter, John Joseph
- Wingerter, John
- Wingo, Hal
- Winius, George
- Winogrand, Garry
- Wise, Bill
- Witt, Linda
- Witte, Michael C.
- Witteman, Paul
- Witteman, Paul A(lan)
- Wittner, Dale
- WO-WY
- Wolander, Robin
- Woodbury, Richard
- Wolfe, Linda
- Wolff, Lothar
- Wolfe, Tom
- Wolmuth, Roger
- Womer, Mike
- Wong, Pearl
- Wood, David
- Wood, Grant
- Wood, John R.
- Wood, Richardson
- Woodcock, Lester
- Woods, Lawrence (Larry)
- Woolf, Samuel Johnson (S.J.)
- Woolley, John Eliot
- Woolley, Knight
- Wootton, Philip
- Worrell, Denise
- Worthy, Ford
- Wouk, Herman
- Wragg, Alan T.
- Wright, Alfred
- Wright, Frank Llyod & Mrs.
- Wright, Frank Lloyd (Box Bio128-Bio129)
- Wright, Henry
- Wylie, Jeff
- Wynn, Wilton
- Wurmstedt, Robert C.
- X-Y-Z
- Yamaguchi, William E.
- Yang, John
- Yevtushenko
- Ying Sita, Sao
- Ylla
- Young, Dave
- Young, Jacob
- Young, J. Paul
- Young, James R.
- Young, Linda
- Young, Marge
- Young, Peter
- Young, Warren
- Yudain, Bernard L.
- Zagorin, Adam
- Zapruder, Abraham
- Zarcone, Beth
- Zeiller, Helen
- Zeno, George
- Zhukov, Georgi
- Zich, Arthur
- Ziegler, Royden M.
- Zim, Marvin
- Zinder, Harry
- Zinsser, William
- Zintl, Robertt (Terry)
- Zoglin, Richard
- Zorthian, Barry
- Zucchi, Daniel E.